Congratulations on making it to this final part of the Data Scientist Nanodegree program.
恭喜你来到了数据科学家纳米学位的最后一个项目！
You've learned a great amount up to this point that covers
目前为止 你已经学到了
so many skills utilized by data scientists in the field.
数据科学家相关的许多技能
You started out by learning about
我们首先学习了
the Data Science Process and the broad steps that need to be taken to
数据科学的完整的大致流程
go from a question of interest all the way to
如何从感兴趣的问题出发
conveying findings to an audience and deploying results.
直至向观众展示你的发现然后将结果部署好
You then learn how to use best practices in software engineering.
之后 你学习了软件工程的一些最佳实践
You learned how to write effective code and how to test your code.
比如 如何高效地编写代码和测试你的代码
You also learned how to write
你还学习了如何编写
object-oriented programs and deploy web applications using Flask.
面向对象的程序和使用 Flask 部署网络应用程序
After that, you're introduced to skills and data engineering.
之后 你学习了数据工程的技能
You completed data and machine learning pipelines that could be used to collect,
完成了数据和机器学习管道的搭建
clean, and organize data for much easier analysis.
用来收集 清洗和整理数据 以便于我们后续的分析
Most recently, you developed your skills with two important applications of
最后 你通过数据科学两个重要的应用：设计实验和推荐引擎
data science techniques: experiment design and recommendation engines.
来进一步提升了技能
Looking at the list of skills covered,
看看目前为止你学过的知识
you should be proud of what you've accomplished up to this point.
你应该为自己的成就感到骄傲
Now, it's time for one final challenge before you
是时候迎接最后一个挑战了
complete the program, the Capstone Project.
完成这个毕业项目后 你就可以从本纳米学位毕业啦
There are many ways to complete this project.
完成这个项目有很多选项 可供选择
You might check out one of
你可以看看
our curated options and see if one of them catches your interest.
我们为你准备的一些备选项目 看是否有你感兴趣的
Some of these topics have been provided by hiring partners,
有些主题是优达的雇主合作方提供的
or you can come up with your own study topic.
你也可以选择自己的研究主题
If there's a particular field that you're interested in,
如果有某个领域你很感兴趣
this is your opportunity to get
请尽情发挥你的创造力来完成一个数据探索项目
some hands-on experience by exploring a data project of your own creation.
这会是一个实践的好机会
Once you've selected a topic,
你选定一个主题之后
you will explore that topic by applying
你需要应用在这个项目中学到的数据科学方法
the key skills in the data science process that you've learned in this program.
来探索该主题
The output will demonstrate your proficiency with data science skills to
最终项目成果需要能展示出你在数据科学方面的专业程度
others and will be a valuable addition to your portfolio.
这也会为你的简历增添亮点
Whatever choice you make,
无论你选择什么项目
you're going to end up with something great.
相信你都会做得很出色
I hope that you're eager to take on the final task of this program.
希望你已经迫不及待要开始你的最后一个项目了
All of us here are excited to see you at the finish line.
预祝你马到成功！